The Paul S. Martin papers, 1910-2006 MS 442
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Series V: Tumamoc Hill Desert Laboratory,1960-2000
  - Tumamoc Hill Desert Laboratory --Planning and policy (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Tumamoc Hill Desert Laboratory --Plant phenology (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Tumamoc Hill Desert Laboratory --Research files (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - Tumamoc Hill Desert Laboratory --Research files (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Tumamoc Hill Desert Laboratory --Research files (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Tumamoc Hill Desert Laboratory --Research files--“Comparative Collection Plants of the Southwest”, 1986 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Tumamoc Hill Desert Laboratory --Research files--Notes (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Tumamoc Hill Desert Laboratory --Smiley, Terah (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Tumamoc Hill Desert Laboratory --Threats to Tumamoc Hill Desert Lab, 1960’s-1980 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Tumamoc Hill Desert Laboratory --Threats to Tumamoc Hill Desert Lab, 1980’s-1990 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Tumamoc Hill Desert Laboratory --Threats to Tumamoc Hill Desert Lab, 1980's-1990 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Tumamoc Hill Desert Laboratory --Threats to Tumamoc Hill Desert Lab--Newspaper clippings (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Tumamoc Hill Desert Laboratory --Threats to Tumamoc Hill Desert Lab--Newspaper clippings (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Tumamoc Hill Desert Laboratory --Tumamoc Hill Desert Lab Advisory Committee (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Tumamoc Hill Desert Laboratory --Tumamoc Hill Desert Lab Advisory Committee (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Tumamoc Hill Desert Laboratory --Tumamoc Hill Desert Lab Advisory Committee (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Tumamoc Hill Desert Laboratory --Tumamoc Hill Desert Lab Advisory Committee (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Tumamoc Hill Desert Laboratory --Tumamoc Hill Desert Lab Advisory Committee (Box 27, Folder 5)
- Series VI: Scrapbooks,1951-1970
  Series note: This series is arranged chronologically.
  - Three scrapbooks, 1951-1960 (Box 28)
  - Three scrapbooks, 1960-1961 (Box 29)
  - Three scrapbooks, 1962-1970 (Box 30)